<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- Projet d'indexation du bro code -->

<brocode ISBN-10="1-4391-1000-X">
	
	
	<article number="001" page="011" keys="chicks">
		<text>
			Bros before ho's.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="002" page="012" keys="stupidity">
		<text>
			A Bro is always entitled to do something stupid, as long as the rest of his Bros are all doing it.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="003" page="013" keys="pets">
		<text>
			If a Bro gets a dog, il must be at least as tall as his knee when full-grown.
		</text>
		<corollary>
			Naming a lapdog after a pro wrestler or a character from a Steve McQueen movie does not a Bro from the spirit of this article.
		</corollary>
	</article>
	
	<article number="004" page="014" keys="brocode, chicks">
		<text>
			A Bro never divulges the existence of the Bro Code to a woman. It is a sacred document not to be shared with chicks for any reason... no, not even that reason.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="005" page="015" keys="sports">
		<text>
			Whether he cares about sports or not, a Bro cares about sports.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="006" page="016" keys="naked">
		<text>
			A Bro shall not lollygag if he must get naked in front of other Bros is a gym locker room.
		</text>
		<corollary>
			If a Bro gets naked in the locker room, all other Bros shall pretend that nothing out of the ordinary is happening while, at the same time, immediately averting their eyes. When in doubt, remember the old adage: "If a towel drops to the floor, so should your eyes."
		</corollary>
	</article>
	
	<article number="007" page="017" keys="cars">
		<text>
			A Bro never admits he can't drive stick. Even after an accident.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="008" page="018" keys="mails">
		<text>
			A Bro never sends a greeting card to another Bro.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="009" page="020" keys="health, jokes">
		<text>
			Should a Bro lose a body part due to an accident or illness, his fellow Bros will not make lame jokes such as "Gimme three!" or "Wow, quitting your job like that really took a lot of ball." It's still a high five and that Bro sill has a lot of balls... metaphorically speaking, of course.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="010" page="021" keys="dumping, chicks">
		<text>
			A Bro will drop whatever he's doing and rush to help his Bro dump a chick.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="011" page="022" keys="moving, furniture">
		<text>
			A Bro may ask his Bro(s) to help him move, but only after first disclosing an honest estiate on both time commitment and number of large pieces of furniture. If the Bro has vastly underestimated either, his Bros retain the right to leave his possessions where they are - in most cases, stuck in a doorway.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="012" page="023" keys="food">
		<text>
			Bros do not share dessert.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="013" page="024" keys="wingman">
		<text>
			All Bros shall dub one of their Bros his wingman.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="014" page="025" keys="chicks, sex">
		<text>
			If a chick inquires about another Bro's sexual history, a Bro shall honor the Brode of Silence and play dumb. Better to have women think all men are stupid than to tell the truth.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="015" page="026" keys="dancing">
		<text>
			A Bro never dances with his hands above his head.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="016" page="027" keys="eye candy, sports">
		<text>
			A Bro should be able, at any time, to recite the following reigning champions: Super Bowl, World Series, and Playmate of the Year.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="017" page="028" keys="work">
		<text>
			A Bro shall be kind and courteous to his co-workers, unless they are beneath him on the Pyramid of Screaming.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="018" page="030" keys="alcohol, party">
		<text>
			If a Bro spearheads a beer run at a party, he is entitled to any excess monies accrued after canvassing the group.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="019" page="031" keys="family, sex">
		<text>
			A Bro shall not sleep with another Bro's sister. However, a Bro shall not get angry if another Bro says, "Dude, your sister's hot!"
		</text>
		<corollary>
			It's probably best for everyone if Bros just hide pictures of their sisters when other Bros are coming over.
		</corollary>
	</article>
	
	<article number="020" page="32" keys="military">
		<text>
			A Bro respects his Bros in the military because they've selflessly chosen to defend the nation, but more to the point, because they can kick his ass six ways to Sunday.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="021" page="033" keys="eye-candy, girlfriends">
		<text>
			A Bro never shares observations about another Bro's smoking-hot girlfriend. Even if the Bro with the hot girlfriend attempts to bait the Bro by saying, "She's smoking-hot, huh?" a Bro shall remain silent, because in this situation, he's the only one who should be baiting.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="022" page="034" keys="woman">
		<text>
			There is no law that prohibits a woman from being a Bro.
		</text>
	</article>
		
	<article number="023" page="036" keys="boobs, TV">
		<text>
			When flipping through TV channels with his Bros, a Bro is not allowed to skip past a program featuring boobs. This includes, but is not limited to, exercise shows, women's athletics, and on some occasions, surgery programs.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="024" page="037" keys="sports, wears">
		<text>
			When wearing a baseball cap, a Bro may position the brim at either 12 or 6 o'clock. All other angles are reserved for rappers and the handicapped.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="025" page="038" keys="chicks, tattoo">
		<text>
			A Bro doesn't let another Bro get a tattoo, particularly a tattoo of a girl's name.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="026" page="041" keys="phone">
		<text>
			Unless he has children, a Bro shall not wear his cell phone on a belt clip.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="027" page="042" keys="naked">
		<text>
			A Bro never removes his shirt in front of other Bros, unless at a resort pool or the beach.
		</text>
		<corollary>
			A Bro with a coat of fur on his back keeps that thing covered at all times, even at a resort pool or the beach. Sorry, Bro.
		</corollary>
	</article>
	
	<article number="028" page="043" keys="chicks, fight">
		<text>
			A Bro will, in a timely manner, alert his Bro to the existence of a girl fight.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="029" page="044" keys="food, movies">
		<text>
			If two Bros decide to catch a movie together, they may not attend a screening that begins after 4:40 PM. Also, despite the cost savings, they shall not split a tub of popcorn, choosing instead to procure individual bags.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="030" page="045" keys="shopping">
		<text>
			A Bro doesn't comparison shop.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="031" page="046" keys="chicks, prowl">
		<text>
			When on the prowl, a Bro hits on the hottest chick first because you just never know.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="032" page="048" keys="age, mariage">
		<text>
			A Bro doesn't allow another Bro to get married until he's at least thirty.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="033" page="049" keys="restroom">
		<text>
			When in a public restroom, a Bro (1) stares straight ahead when using the urinal; (2) makes the obligatory comment, "What is this, a chicks' restroom?" if there are more than two dres waiting to pee; and (3) attempts to shoot his used paper towel intro the trash can like a basketball... rebounding is optional.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="034" page="050" keys="sex">
		<text>
			Bros cannot make eye contact during a devil's threeway.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="035" page="051" keys="movies">
		<text>
			A Bro never rents a chick flick.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="036" page="052" keys="boobs">
		<text>
			When questioned in the company of women, a Bro always decries fake breasts.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="037" page="054" keys="politeness">
		<text>
			A Bro is under no obligation to open a door for anyone. If women insist on having their own professional basketball league, then they can open their own doors. Honestly, they're not that heavy.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="038" page="055" keys="fight, groin">
		<text>
			Even in a fight to the death, a Bro never punchers another Bro in the groin.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="039" page="056" keys="chicks, phone">
		<text>
			When a Bro gets a chick's number, he waits at least ninety-six hours before calling her.
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="040" page="057" keys="mariage, party">
		<text>
			Should a Bro become stricken with engagment, his Bros shall stage an intervention and attempt to heal him. This is more commonly known as "a bachelor party".
		</text>
	</article>
	
	<article number="041" page="059" keys="crying">
		<text>
			A Bro never cries.
		</text>
		<exception>
			Watching Field of Dreams, E.T., or a sports legend retire (apply only to the first time he retires).
		</exception>
	</article>
	
	
	
</brocode>